我们,是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
珊迪之歌
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
presisco
翻译
零玖/presisco
校对
presisco
特效
压制
presisco
给你得,拉尔斯哥们!
Here you arez, my larz!
呃,我给你放这了
Uh, I'll just leave it here for you.
珊迪,我亲爱的小姐!
Sadie, my lady!
我在想我能不能
I was wondering if I could hang
将一张沙滩狂欢节的传单贴在-
one of these beach-a-palooza flyers in --
珊迪?珊迪!
Sadie? Sadie!
我难免引人注目
♪ I can't help it if I make a scene ♪
即使走下我的艳粉礼车
♪ stepping out of my hot-pink limousine ♪
我甩甩头就能阻塞车流
♪ I'm turning heads, and I'm stopping traffic ♪
万众为造型尖叫,为玩笑捧腹
♪ when I pose, they scream, and when I joke, they laugh ♪
我有一双令人失神的眼
♪ I've got a pair of eyes that they're getting lost in ♪
魔鬼的步伐迷惑人心
♪ they're hypnotized by my way of walking ♪
我犹如魔术师般炫目
♪ I got them dazzled like a stage magician ♪
万众望我所指,听我谈笑风生
♪ when I point, they look, and when I talk, they listen ♪
大家都需要朋友
♪ well, everybody needs a friend ♪
而我有你和你和你
♪ and I've got you and you and you ♪
如此之多都忘记名字
♪ so many, I can't even name them ♪
只能说我
♪ can you blame me?
如此有名
♪ I'm too famous
唱得好!喔!
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
耶!那真是太好听了!
Yeah! That was amazing!
呜呼呼!赞!
Ooh-hoo-hoo! Awesome!
不,呃,我只是-我没在-
No, heh. I was just -- I wasn't --
啊!呃...
Heh. Mm.
我居然不知道你会唱歌
I didn't know you could sing.
没人知道,你需要什么吗?
Nobody does. So, um, do you need something?
哦!
Oh!
我只是帮笑脸先生四处
I'm just going around helping Mr. Smiley
发散今年的狂欢节传单
hand out fliers for beach-a-palooza this year.
你应该报名的!
You should sign up!
呃...为什么?
Ehh, why?
呃...因为你声音很好听?
Ehh...Because your voice is beautiful!
啊,其实任何人唱这首歌都会很好听
Aw, anybody'd sound fine singing along with that song.
它非常容易,非常俗,而且-而且很洗脑,而且-
It's so cheesy and dumb and -- and catchy,and--
我知道每句歌词
I know every single word.
太好了!
Perfect!
现在你只需要日程了
Now you just need a routine.
我-我能给你设计一个
I can help you put one together.
噢,真的?
Aw, really?
你认为人们愿意听我唱歌?
You think people would want to hear me sing?
他们当然愿意啊!你唱的非常好!
Of course they would! You're great!
另外,镇上的每个人都会参加!
Besides, everyone in town is doing something!
对啊,你猜怎么着?是啊!
Yeah. You know what? Yeah!
谁在乎呢,对不对?
Who cares, right?
我在害怕什么?
What am I afraid of?
这-这会很有趣的!
Th-this could be fun!
你的家很不错嘛
Your house is so cool.
就在这下面
Just down here.
喔!
Whoa!
你睡地下室吗?
Were you sleep in a basement?
我更愿意称作"地堡"
I like to think of it like a bunker.
这些都是你的吗?
Are these all yours?
是的,但那些也不能算我的
Yeah, but they're not really my thing.
你想要的话可以拿一个
You can have one if you want.
呃...我可不想拆散一个家庭
Ehhhhh, I don't want to break up a family.
那么,我们有唱片了
So, now we have the cd.
我觉得我可以练习唱歌了
I guess I can practice singing.
首先我们得确定你要穿什么
First, we got to figure out what you're gonna wear.
这重要吗?
Does it matter?
自从我两年前的某次裸奔后,
Ever since my act two years ago,
就多了条必须穿衣服的规矩
there's been a rule that you've got to wear clothes.
我本来也没想着穿内衣去
I wasn't planning to go in my underwear.
要不搞点炫的?
How about something flashy?
闪闪发光
And sparkly.
或者,你觉得你的噱头是什么?
O-or wait, what do you think should be your gimmick?
喔,不不不
Whoa. No, no, no.
不要有噱头,唱歌已经有点复杂了
No gimmicks. The singing's already a stretch.
也许...这个?
Maybe...This?
或者也可以-
Or maybe even --
那个很不错!
that one's pretty!
呃,我觉得这有点复杂了
Eh, I think it's a little much.
右下角有只甘特哦！能看到吗？
我还是弄点我喜欢的吧
I'll just do something comfortable.
那是什么?
What's that?!
我们下次再说!
We'll do this another time!
嘿!珊迪!
Hey, Sadie!
嗨,妈妈,你回家早了啊
Hi, mom. You're home early.
我专门提前回家给你看这个!
I just had to rush home to show you this!
看看这个专门给你的小家伙!
Look at this little guy I got for you!
它是不是超可爱?
Ain't he the cutest?
哦,谢谢,妈妈
Oh. Thanks mom.
珊迪,你和格雷格的孩子在一起干嘛?
Sadie, what are you doing hanging out with Greg's boy?
芭伯,我知道你送邮件,
Barb, I knew you delivered mail,
但我不知道是你送的珊迪啊!(deliver:送货/生孩子)
but I didn't know you delivered Sadie!
没错,我妈是邮递员
Yeah, my mom's the mailman.
就是我!
That she is!
局里最棒的邮递员,妇女,或者野兽!
Best dang mailman, woman, or animal on the force!
至少在他们发现我从丢失信件箱里拿信件前是!
At least until they catch me taking from the "lost mail" bin!
但这只是我们的小秘密,对吧?
But that's between us, heh?
那么,史蒂文,你和我女儿在一起是为什么?
So, Steven, what are your intentions with my daughter?
我们在为沙滩呜呜呜准备舞台秀
We're planning a stage show for beach-a-pawooza.
沙滩呜呜呜!
Beach-a-pawooza!
那是什么?
What was that?
我要在沙滩狂欢节上唱歌
I'm going to sing a song for beach-a-palooza.
蛤?
What?!
哦哦哦哦!
Oh, oh, oh oh!
珊迪,你要去唱歌?!
Sadie, you're gonna sing?!
对
Yeah.
那么干吧!
Then come on!
我们现在就得开始准备!
We have to start planning now!
史蒂文,帮我找套装束!
Steven, help me find an outfit!
没问题!
Okay!
呃,其实,我完全可以自己完成啊
Uh, you know, I could probably do this by myself.
不麻烦!我们愿意帮你忙!
It's no trouble. We'd love to help ya out!
对吧,史蒂文?
Right, Steven?
没错!
Right!
哦,看!
Oh, look!
这是你原来的芭蕾舞服!
It's your old ballet outfit!
你还会芭蕾舞?
You're a ballerina?
当我还,10岁,时
When I was like 10.
喔!这是你的泳衣!
Oh, it's your swimsuit!
她原来是个很强的游泳选手!
She used to be a competitive swimmer!
保持了大概一个月,在我11岁时
For like a month. When I was 11.
芭伯,这是什么?
Barb, what's this?
噢!看,看!
Oh! Look, look!
记得我曾开车带你去玩垒球吗?
Remember when I used to drive you to your softball games?
...我只记得你打了裁判
I remember when you punched the umpire.
这就是他试图当黑裁判阻止我女儿双杀的下场!
That's what he gets for trying to cheat my daughter out of a double!
而之后我则被联盟禁赛了
And then I wasn't really allowed in the league anymore.
他们才该被封禁!
Them's the breaks!
那么我们目前为表演准备多少了?
So what have you got planned so far for your show?
一点没有,我猜
Nothing, I guess.
Well, don't you worry!
我和史蒂文会替你搞定演出的!
Me and Steven will figure out your show for you!
我们会确保你的歌声传遍全球!
We'll make sure the world will hear your voice!
呃,我们能不能别这么复杂?
Well, let's just try to keep it simple?
什么?
What was that?
我难免引人注目
♪ I can't help it if I make a scene ♪
即使走下我的艳粉礼车
♪ stepping out of my hot-pink limousine ♪
我甩甩头就能阻塞车流
♪ I'm turning heads, and I'm stopping traffic ♪
万众为造型尖叫,为玩笑捧腹
♪ when I pose, they scream, and when I joke, they laugh ♪
我有一双令人失神的眼
♪ I've got a pair of eyes that they're getting lost in ♪
魔鬼的步伐迷惑人心
♪ they're hypnotized by my way of walking ♪
我犹如魔术师般炫目
♪ I got them dazzled like a stage magician ♪
万众望我所指,听我谈笑风生
♪ when I point, they look, and when I talk, they listen ♪
大家都需要朋友
♪ well, everybody needs a friend ♪
而我有你和你和你
♪ and I've got you and you and you ♪
如此之多都忘记名字
♪ so many, I can't even name them ♪
只能说我
♪ can you blame me?
如此有名
♪ I'm too famous
我觉得我们做的很棒!
I think we did an excellent job!
我们只需要再找笑脸先生,让他把名字加到传单里
We just need to tell Mr. Smiley to add her name to the flier.
哦,也许不用把我名字放在上边吧
Oh, maybe don't put my name on it.
对啊!如果她作为神秘嘉宾呢?
Yeah! What if she was a surprise?!
这真是个好主意!
That's a great idea!
她将作为神秘的压轴表演!
She'll be a mystery final act!
特约神秘嘉宾
谢谢大家参与沙滩狂欢节!
Thank you, beach-a-palooza!
你们能从下一组表演者的工作猜到是谁--她们白天可在送披萨哦!
You know this next act from their day job, delivering Pizza!
但今晚,她们来这里送段子了!
But tonight, they're delivering jokes!
刚才就是个笑话
That was a joke.
让我们献上掌声,
Let me hear a big round of applause
欢迎奇奇与她的口技同伴笨笨!
for Kiki and her ventriloquist dummy!
奇奇,笑脸先生刚才粗鲁的叫我笨笨!
Kiki, that rude Mr. Smiley just called me a dummy!
那只是表演,奶奶!
That's just our act, gunga!
为什么不向大家讲个笑话?
Why don't you show them your jokes?
披萨怎么系鞋带?
How does a Pizza tie its shoes?
如何?
How?
用蒜蓉面包"结"啊!
With a garlic knot!
好啦
All right.
我们快要揭晓今晚的神秘嘉宾了
Well, we're getting closer to tonight's mystery guest.
即使我也不知道是谁--我可是主持人诶!
Even I don't know who it is, and I'm the host!
但首先,有请罗纳多·弗莱曼
But first, Ronaldo Fryman with a lecture
讲解"石头人类:鉴别与防护"
on "rock people: Identification and defense."
我不敢相信
I can't believe it.
传单真的起作用了!
The fliers really worked!
整个小镇都来了!还有些外地人!
The whole town is here! Plus some!
哦,我的珊迪!
Oh, my Sadie!
真是个巨星啊!
Such a big star!
以前甚至都没去过毕业舞会,但看看现在!
Never even went to the prom and look at ya now!
珊迪脸上有颗星的造型模仿了《杰姆和全息图》中的杰姆
到我了吗?
Am I on yet?
珊迪·米勒!
Sadie Miller!
你是神秘嘉宾?
You're the mystery guest?
珊迪的装束与《魔法俏佳人》中的仙灵类似
我完全猜不出来啊!
I never even would've recognized you!
哦!
Oh!
嗨,笑脸先生,呃...
Hi, Mr. Smiley. Uh
你-呃-你好?
How, uh, how are you?
我很好,但看起来有人
I'm fine, but it looks like someone here
有点怯场啊
has a case of the showbiz shakes.
你知道我的一个老朋友告诉过我什么?
You know what an old friend of mine told me once?
伸手不打笑脸人
A little smile never hurt anybody.
啊～看起来好极了!
Awwww, lookin good!
谢谢!
Thank you!
多点亮粉!
More sparkles!
好的!
Yes, sir!
下一位,先生们,女士们
Next up, ladies and gentlemen,
你们和俺的邮递员!
your mailman and "mime!"
杰米!
Jamie!
哦,是那个盒子的表演
Oh, it's a box.
右上角的观众穿的衣服看出来没？
他-他-他要假扮一个盒子
He's -- he's -- he's doing a box.
难不成是Snake的拿手戏？
呃哦,没亮粉了
Uh-oh. No more glitter.
我得跑去拿车里的紧急备品了
I'll have to run and get the emergency supply from the car.
守护我女儿,史蒂文
Guard my girl, Steven.
珊迪,回来!
Sadie, come back here!
我等不及要看神秘嘉宾了!
I can't wait for this mystery act!
你认为会是杂技吗?
You think it's a juggler?
也许他们会玩弄些锋利的东西
Maybe they'll juggle something sharp.
我得准备好手机,万一有人搞砸了呢?
I'm gonna have my phone ready in case someone gets hurt.
珊迪!
Sadie!
我-我没法呼吸了!
I-I can't breathe!
好吧,好吧,如果你不打算回来
Okay, okay, if you're not gonna come back
让我为你准备好,那么我们可以准备舞蹈
and let me work on you, then let's work on the routine.
好吧,就让我
Okay, just let me --
哦,不!
oh, no!
你毁了我画的口红!
You ruined my lipstick!
别害怕,史蒂文在此!
Never fear! Steven's here!
呃啊啊～～呃啊!!!
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
珊迪,你在干嘛?
Sadie, why did you do that?
啊!因为!
Rah! Because!
你和我妈妈一样遭!
You're just as bad as my mom!
什么?
What?!
求求你,妈妈,不要逼我做这个
Please, mom, don't make me do this.
逼你?你说过你想要唱歌
Make you? You said you wanted to sing!
是的!
Yeah!
我说过!我说过!我说过!我说过!
I did! I did! I did! I did!
就像我说过的很多事情!
Just like I say lots of things!
就像,"嘿,妈妈,游泳看起来很有趣!"
Like, "hey, mom, swimming looks fun!"
接着Boom!
Then bam!
突然间我要参加400米接力
Suddenly, I'm anchoring a 400-meter relay
作为沙滩市的队员了!
for the Beach City seals!
"嘿,妈妈,我认为报名参加垒球会很好!"
"Hey, mom, I thought signing up for softball would be nice!"
过了六个生日,
Six birthdays later,
我仍然只能收到护膝和击球头盔!
I'm still getting nothing but kneepads and batting helmets!
"嘿,妈妈,我想在今年的沙滩狂欢节上唱歌,"
"Hey, mom, I want to sing in this year's beach-a-palooza,"
然后我得到了什么?这个!
and what do I get? This!
我只想有那么一次,能有点自主性,
I just thought for once, I'd get to do things my way,
但你搅和了进来,直接接管了一切,就像你一直做的一样
but you came in and took over everything, like you always do.
我只想让所有人知道我女儿多么有才华
I just wanted everyone to know how talented my daughter is.
这,不是你女儿
This is not your daughter.
我对不起,我-
I'm sorry. I --
接下来,你们一直在期待的
Next up, the one you've all been waiting for.
万众期待!独一无二!
The one! The only!
神秘嘉宾!
Mystery guest!
啊啊啊啊!我怎么沦落到如此境地?
Aaah! How did I let this happen?
我不想这么做!
I don't want to do this!
从来都不是你
You never did.
其实一直是我
It was always me.
掌声欢迎...
Give it up for...
看来你应验了,奶奶
Looks like you called it, gunga.
那个"神秘嘉宾"的宣传完全就是史蒂文的风格
That "mystery guest" bit had Steven written all over it.
我难免引人注目
♪ I can't help it if I make a scene ♪
即使走下我的艳粉礼车
♪ stepping out of my hot-pink limousine ♪
我甩甩头就能阻塞车流
♪ I'm turning heads, and I'm stopping traffic ♪
万众为造型尖叫,为玩笑捧腹
♪ when I pose, they scream, and when I joke, they laugh ♪
我有一双令人失神的眼
♪ I've got a pair of eyes that they're getting lost in ♪
魔鬼的步伐迷惑人心
♪ they're hypnotized by my way of walking ♪
我犹如魔术师般炫目
♪ I got them dazzled like a stage magician ♪
万众望我所指,听我谈笑风生
♪ when I point, they look, and when I talk, they listen ♪
大家都需要朋友
♪ well, everybody needs a friend ♪
而我有你和你和你
♪ and I've got you and you and you ♪
如此之多都忘记名字
♪ so many, I can't even name them ♪
只能说我
♪ can you blame me?
如此有名
♪ I'm too famous
你是否注意我是那天上明星?
Haven't you noticed that I'm a star?
当地球旋转我进入你的视野
I'm coming into view as the world is turning.
你是否注意到我已如此成功?
Haven't you noticed I've made it this far?
现在所有人能看我闪耀
Now, everyone can see me burning.
我认为我非常卑微
♪ I always thought I might be bad ♪
现在我已确定
♪ now I'm sure that it's true
因,你如此完美
♪ 'cause I think you're so good ♪
而我却丝毫不如
♪ and I'm nothing like you